<?xml version="1.0"?>
<xml>
		<ver>1.10.9.9</ver>
    <log>If there is an update when the file file is missing, go to Steam Client - Library List - mydockfinder - right-click menu - Properties - Local File - Verify software file integrity
If the desktop icon is not displayed after enabling pre-stage scheduling, you can right-click on the desktop-view-display desktop icon to enable display desktop icon
	    If using MSI afterburner will cause irregular freezing or crashing issues, you can set it in MSI afterburner, add dock_64.exe, then select dock_64.exe, and finally select "None" on the right side.
	   Changelog
1.Added a debug mode toggle, which can be enabled in Preferences - Global Settings.
2.Fixed a freeze crash caused by using the UWP message loop in the previous version.
3.Fixed a freezing issue in all previous versions when a large number of windows were generated in the background by certain programs (e.g., IDM batch background downloads).
4.Fixed overexposure of the launcher background after enabling HDR in all previous versions.
5.Fixed too dark color rendering in gradient blur effects after enabling HDR.
6.Fixed crashes in all previous versions caused by multithreaded modifications of dock icon data.
7.Fixed crashes caused by gradient blur effects in window previews.
8.Fixed misaligned window-switching animations when too many windows are listed in the front dispatch window list.
9.Fixed misalignment of launcher icons in portrait mode.
10.Added the ability to add non-fullscreen applications. After adding a non-fullscreen application, the dock and Finder can be activated when this program window is in fullscreen, in Preferences - Window Management.
11.Added the ability to add game applications. After adding a game application, DLL injection will not be used to intercept minimize window animations and show/hide window animations, ensuring smooth gameplay. It also allows the dock and Finder to automatically restart when a fullscreen game is running in windowed fullscreen mode, in Preferences - Window Management.
</xml>
