<?xml version="1.0"?>
<xml>
		<ver>1.12</ver>
    <log>If there is an update when the file file is missing, go to Steam Client - Library List - mydockfinder - right-click menu - Properties - Local File - Verify software file integrity
If the desktop icon is not displayed after enabling pre-stage scheduling, you can right-click on the desktop-view-display desktop icon to enable display desktop icon
	    If using MSI afterburner will cause irregular freezing or crashing issues, you can set it in MSI afterburner, add dock_64.exe, then select dock_64.exe, and finally select "None" on the right side.
	   Changelog
1.Added a toggle in myfinder monitoring to highlight when usage is too high. The previous version was enabled by default; this update adds a switch that can be turned on in Preferences - Monitoring.
2.Fixed the issue where Dock would freeze when Immersive Mode and icon reflection were enabled simultaneously.
3.Fixed freezes caused by Dock icons.
4.Fixed occasional failures in input method detection and switching in all previous versions.
5.Fixed high CPU usage when the system Recycle Bin had too many files causing Dock monitoring to detect files.
6.Optimized the Dock high-quality icon rendering feature, no longer requiring a program restart.
7.Optimized Dock to show window icons for programs when some exe programs do not have icons, for all previous versions.
8.Rewrote gradient blur HLSL files. Previous versions’ non-D2D-specific rendering code could cause exceptions, now compiled as D2D HLSL code.
9.Fixed occasional refresh issues with the myfinder tray.
10.Fixed icon rendering anomalies when minimized to Dock in the previous version.
11.Fixed some systems incorrectly recognizing exe programs as UWP.
12.Fixed freeze issues after sleep wake-up (experimental).
13.Fixed an issue in the previous version where minimized Dock icons would show minimized windows after GPU adapter reset.
14.Added VRAM management feature to periodically clean up unused VRAM resources.
15.Fixed rendering not filling completely when myfinder monitoring curve usage is at 100.
16.Fixed crashes caused by GPU adapter resets in all previous versions (experimental).
17.Rewrote some forced GPU rendering code to software CPU rendering to prevent crashes caused by certain GPU driver anomalies (e.g., multi-screen).
18.Encapsulated some Composition low-level code to prevent freezes after exceptions.
19.Optimized Dock icon rendering performance.
20.Fixed Dockfinder freezes caused by some programs not responding in all previous versions.
21.Fixed freezes caused when adding minimized windows to the foreground scheduler.
22.Fixed foreground scheduler issue where the window list could not be activated by mouse in multi-screen setups.
23.Fixed icon position misalignment when switching pages in Launchpad and moving between multiple screens.
24.Fixed other issues.
</xml>
